<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rosary Bank</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Register</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your email and password or sign up</string>
    <string name="new_user">Please register in Rosary Bank with your email and any password</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="send_password_reset_email">Send Password reset email</string>
    <string name="remove_user">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="new_pass">New Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Firebase</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Get registered in Rosary Bank now!</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registered. Login Me!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reset_password">ResetPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="btn_forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_back"><![CDATA[<< Back]]></string>
    <string name="hint_new_email">New Email</string>
    <string name="btn_change">Change</string>
    <string name="btn_send">Send</string>
    <string name="btn_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="lbl_forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">Please enter your registered Email Id to sent you password reset instructions.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">RegisterActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">RegistrationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_deposit_rosary">DepositRosaryActivity</string>
    <string name="account_balance"><u>Account Summary</u></string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-7271379408439527/4448521952</string>
    <string name="Rewardvideo_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-7271379408439527/7826956778</string>
    <string name="Fullpage_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-7271379408439527/7369460073</string>

    <string name="testvideo_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/5224354917</string>

    <string name="app_id"> ca-app-pub-7271379408439527~6992415500</string>


    <string-array name="rosary_type">
        <item>Normal Rosary</item>
        <item>Mercy Rosary</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rosary_request_type">
        <item>Normal</item>
        <item>Urgent</item>
        <item>Critical</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dedicated_to">
        <item>Rosary Bank</item>
        <item>Other People</item>
        <item>Organisation</item>
        <item>Personal</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Request_Queue_type">
        <item>Global</item>
        <item>JesusYouth</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">1960893827462071</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notification">NotificationActivity</string>
    <string name="my_cart">Notifications</string>
    <string name="delete">DELETE</string>


    <!-- Rosary Prayer-->
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">DEVOTIONAL PRAYERS</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">All the Christian Prayers</string>


    <string name="title_activity_rosary_prayer">RosaryPrayer</string>
    <string name="rosary_english_annunciation">
        "The time for the Incarnation is at hand.
        Of all women God prepared Mary from her conception to be the Mother of the Incarnate Word.
        The Angel Gabriel announces: Hail, full of grace! The Lord is with thee.
        Mary wonders at this salutation.
        The Angel assures her: "Fear not .. you shall conceive in your womb, and give birth to a Son."
        Mary is troubled for she has made a vow of virginity.
        The Angel answers that she will conceive by the power of the Holy Spirit, and her Son will be called the Son of God.
        The Incarnation awaits Mary's consent.
        Mary answers: "Behold the handmaid of the Lord. Be it done unto me according to your word."
        The Word was made flesh and dwelt among us.

        Dear Mary, when the angel gave you a message that God wanted you to conceive Jesus, the savior,
        you said yes to Him without questioning your well-being.  You were engaged to Joseph,
        you knew you could be stoned to death,  you knew people would not like you,
        but you trusted God fully because you knew He knows better and has your best interest at heart no matter what happens.
        Even if you would suffer. Pray for me too, that I may be humble like you and accept God's Will in my life,
        no matter what that is. Also, pray for me that I may have the discernment to know His Will,
        and to live as a reflection of His commandments, especially the greatest of all Jesus left us,
        "Love God above, and neighbor as I love myself"!

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_visitation">
        "Mary's cousin Elizabeth conceived a son in her old age.. for nothing is impossible with God.
        Charity prompts Mary to hasten to visit Elizabeth in the hour of her need.
        The journey to Elizabeth's home is about eighty miles requiring four or five days.
        Though long and arduous, the journey is joyous, for Mary bears with her the Incarnate Word.
        At Mary's salutation, John the Baptist is sanctified in his mother's womb.
        Elizabeth exclaims: "Blessed are you among women, and blessed is the fruit of your womb."
        "How have I deserved that the mother of my Lord should come to me?"
        "Blessed is she who believed that the "Lord's" words to her would be fulfilled."
        Mary replies: "My soul proclaims the greatness of the Lord, and my spirit finds joy in God my Savior."
        Mary serves her cousin in all humility for three months until the birth of John the Baptist.

        Dear Mary even though you were pregnant, you rushed to go to help your cousin Elizabeth who needed more help.
        Despite your cousin being older, she knelt before you calling you "Blessed Among Women",
        honored that the Mother of God would visit her. Dear Mother, teach me to love like you,
        and remind me and the whole world how much you love us; how much God the Father and Jesus the Son love us.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_nativity">
        "Joseph and Mary go to Bethlehem to comply with the decree of Caesar Augustus.
        The hour for Mary to give birth is near, but there is no room in the inn.
        In the stillness of the night, the Savior is born in a cave, Mary remaining a Virgin.
        She wraps Him in swaddling clothes and lays Him in a manger.
        In unspeakable joy Mary gathers to her bosom the Flower of her virginity.
        Jesus enters the world in poverty to teach the lesson of detachment from earthly things.
        The angel announces to the shepherds: "Today there is born to you in the town of David a Savior, Who is Christ the Lord."
        The angelic chorus sing: "Glory to God in the highest, and peace to His people on earth."
        The shepherds come to the stable to pay homage to the Infant Jesus.
        The Magi come to adore the Holy Child and offer Him gifts.

        Dear Jesus, you were born in a poor place, because hotels couldn't give your mother and St. Joseph a place to have you.
        Even though you were Almighty and Son of God the Father, you didn't push or impose your power,
        you were born among the poor who welcomed you, in a stable, with the Shepherds.
        Please dear Jesus help me to be simple and gentle like you and God the Father,
        help me never to impose my will, power or strength on others. Help me to respect others,
        especially the poor. Mother Mary who had a baby in such an uncomfortable place,
        remind me to be calm no matter what turbulence I might find in this life.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_presentation">
        "Observing the law of Moses they take Jesus to the temple to present Him to the Lord.
        According to the Law the firstborn male child of every family should be consecrated to the Lord.
        Mary offers her Son to the Father, then ransoms Him back at the price paid by the poor.
        Jesus is not subject to the law of Moses, yet to teach obedience, submits to it.
        Mary is not subject to the law of purification, yet in humility she submits to it.
        God had revealed to Simeon that he would not see death until he had seen the Messiah.
        Recognizing the Child, he prays: "Now you can dismiss your servant in peace. You have fulfilled your word."
        "This Child is destined to be the downfall and rise of many in Israel, a sign that will be opposed."
        And to Mary Simeon reveals: "And your own soul a sword shall pierce."
        After they fulfill all the Law requires they return to Nazareth.

        Dear Jesus you respected the culture of blessings for children,
        and you inspired your parents to do the same as everyone else. And yet you were God Himself.
        Through the prayer of the Rosary, I am constantly reminded about your simplicity,
        your deep love for me and all of us. You came to live among us, and became like us,
        to teach us to live this life. Please help me to know how to love you back and
        to appreciate the sacrifice you made to leave Heaven and come on earth.
        Teach me to respect the law of my country and my church even when I feel opposed.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_findingjesus">
        "When Jesus is twelve years old, He goes with His parents to Jerusalem for the feast of the Passover.
        After the feast of the Passover, Joseph and Mary unknowingly set out for Nazareth without Jesus.
        At the end of the first day's journey they discover Jesus is missing.
        His parents return immediately looking for Him.
        This loss causes grief and anxiety beyond our understanding to the hearts of Mary and Joseph.
        On the third day they find Jesus in the Temple among the Doctors who were astonished at His wisdom.
        Mary: "Son, why have you done this to us? Your father and I have been searching for You in sorrow."
        Jesus: "Why did you search for Me? Did you not know that I must be about My "Father's" business?"
        Jesus goes down with them to Nazareth, and is subject to them.
        Mary keeps all these things in her heart.

        Dear Jesus, you stayed behind in the temple preaching about your Father, and 3 days went by,
        even though you wanted to be with your mother and father, you knew you came on a mission to serve your Father
        and earn souls for heaven. Help me to put God first in my life, in my work, even when things are not going as I wish.
        Mother Mary, pray for me that I know how to deal with pain as graciously as you did in your life and
        please help to find and imitate Jesus in all I do, that I may do all with unselfish love.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_agony">
        "Jesus comes with his disciples to Gethsemani: "Stay here, while I go yonder and pray."
        Entering the garden with Peter, James, and John, Jesus prays, "My soul is sorrowful unto death."
        Jesus sees the sins of all mankind, whose guilt He has taken upon Himself.
        He sees the wrath of the Father which His sufferings must appease.
        So great is his anguish that His sweat becomes as drops of blood falling to the ground.
        An angel appears to Him from heaven to strengthen Him.
        "Father, if it be possible, let this cup pass from Me; yet, not My will but Yours be done."
        Finding the disciples asleep: "Could you not watch one hour with me?"
        Jesus is betrayed by Judas, cruelly bound and led away.
        Father, by the merits of the agony of Jesus in the Garden, have mercy on us and on the whole world.

        Dear Jesus, You lived 33 years among us, knowing what would happen to you, and yet you kept going,
        you had power you could have used to avoid this much suffering but you accepted it all to save us.
        You sweat blood thinking of how you would die so badly the next day. You asked your Father in your
        agony to take away the suffering, but brought yourself back quickly, and asked Him to let His Will be done in you,
        not yours. Help me to also want God's Will, your will, to be done in my life, not mine.
        Teach me how to control myself even when I know I can change the situation,
        give me the strength to do what is right in the eyes of God alone.
        Forgive me my sins that caused you that much pain, and thank you for loving me that much.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_scourging">
        "Jesus is taken before the High Priest where He is falsely accused, buffeted and insulted.
        The Jewish leaders take Jesus before Pilate, for only he can impose the death penalty.
        The robber, Barabbas, is preferred to Jesus.
        Pilate can "find no cause in Him", yet to appease the Jews, he orders Jesus to be scourged.
        The scourge is made of leather thongs to which are attached small sharp bones.
        Jesus is bound to a pillar and cruelly scourged until His whole body is covered with deep wounds.
        The Lamb of God offers His suffering for the sins of mankind.
        Jesus suffers so much in His sacred flesh to satisfy, especially, for sins of the flesh.
        The prophecy of Isaiah is fulfilled: "He was wounded for our iniquities, He was bruised for our sins."
        Father, by the merits of Jesus in this painful scourging, have mercy on us and on the whole world.

        Dear Jesus, I am so sorry that one for whom you gave your life, betrayed you. You were beaten up so badly,
        they tore up your skin, they didn't have mercy for you, and they hurt you to please themselves.
        You have done nothing to deserve such punishment, willingly accepted for my sake. Please dear Jesus,
        help me to love you, to appreciate you, and never allow me to complain about injustice done to me,
        but to love beyond the cross.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_crowning">
        "Pilate asks, "Are You a king?" Jesus answers: "I am a King, but My kingdom is not of this world."
        In the praetorium, the soldiers place an old purple robe on Jesus in mockery of His claim to be a king.
        They fashion a crown out of thorns, and forcefully press it down upon His head.
        In His bound hands they place a reed, as a sceptre, in mockery of His kingship.
        Kneeling before Him in derision, they spit on Him, and cry out: "Hail, King of the Jews!"
        Taking the reed from His hand they strike Him on the head, driving the thorns more deeply into His scalp.
        Pilate brings Jesus before the people, hoping His pitiful sight will soften them: "Behold the man!"
        Their response: "Crucify Him! Crucify Him!"
        Our Blessed Lord submitted to this terrible humiliation to make reparation for our pride.
        Father, by the merits of this painful humiliation, have mercy on us and on the whole world.

        My Dear King, You were mocked after they beat you, and crowned you with thorns and yet you were the TRUE king.
        With the pain and humiliation you felt, you didn't respond to anything unkindly.
        You did what your human strength allowed, without uttering a word of insult or complaint,
        or using your Godly power. You had me and my brothers and sisters instead to defend and protect.
        Hoping we would listen to your warnings, accept your sacrifice and make a better choice to be with you
        one day in a paradise forever. Help me to remain in truth,
        to support truth and acknowledge truth even when I am wrong. Allow me to trust you,
        to accept my sufferings and offer them to you, and never let my sufferings make me do wrong.
        Help me to forgive always and never strike back.  You are the just judge, you will defend me.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_carrying">
        "One condemned to death by crucifixion is forced to carry the cross to the place of execution.
        The suffering of Jesus is intense as the cross is laid on His bruised and wounded back and shoulders.
        Weak and exhausted from loss of blood, lack of food and rest, Jesus falls three times under the cross.
        Jesus meets His afflicted Mother causing untold anguish in the Hearts of Son and Mother.
        The countenance of Jesus is disfigured with blood and sweat, with dust and spittle.
        Veronica wipes His face, leaving on her towel the image of His countenance.
        Fearing that Jesus might die on the way, the soldiers force Simon of Cyrene to carry the cross behind Jesus.
        Jesus speaks to weeping women: "Weep not for Me, but for yourselves and your children."
        "If anyone is to be My disciple, let him take up his cross and follow Me."
        Father, by the merits of this painful journey to Calvary, have mercy on us and on the whole world.

        Dear Jesus, You carried the cross over the wounds of the beatings and thorns.
        I am so sorry for what you had to go through. You fell down many times, at the heaviness of your cross
        and you rose again. Dear Jesus, you are the most loving being that ever lived, you took all that willingly,
        for me and everyone else. It was not a quick death, they tortured you all day, and you still remained kind.
        You met your mother on the way which gave you strength to have Her support but also pain to see Her suffering so badly.
        Teach me to love Her and to love you. Mother Mary, you who saw everything, thank Him for me,
        kiss His scars for me, and remind that despite my sins I love Him.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_crucifixion">
        "The hands and feet of Jesus are nailed to the cross in the presence of His afflicted Mother.
        "Father, forgive them for they know not what they do."
        "This day you will be with Me in paradise."
        "Woman, behold your son. Son, behold your Mother."
        "My God, My God, why have You forsaken Me?"
        "I thirst."
        "It is finished."
        "Father, into Your hands I commend My spirit."
        The side of Jesus is pierced with a lance. His body is taken down and placed in the arms of His Mother.
        Father, by the merits of the crucifixion and death of Jesus, have mercy on us and on the whole world.

        Dear Jesus, Before you died you forgave those who killed you, teaching us to forgive without measure.
        In the middle of such crushing pain, you gave us your mother Mary to also be our Mother so she could
        comfort us as she comforted you. Please remind me the price you paid for me so I can remember this all my life,
        remind me to obey you and help me to remember every word you said and try to put it in practice.
        Like the thief on your right side, I am not worthy for heaven but please remember me
        when I get to your kingdom and have mercy on all the sinners.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_resurrection">
        "The body of Jesus is placed in the tomb on the evening of Good Friday.
        His soul descends into the realm of the dead to announce to the Just the tidings of their redemption.
        Fearing the body of Jesus will be taken, the chief priests place guards at the tomb.
        On the third day Jesus rises from the dead, glorious and immortal.
        The earth quakes as the angel rolls back the stone, the guards flee in terror.
        The holy women coming to anoint the body of Jesus are amazed and frightened to find the tomb open.
        An angel calms their fears: "He is not here. He has risen as He said."
        Jesus appears to Mary Magdalen and Peter and two disciples on the way to Emmaus.
        That evening He appears to the apostles behind locked doors: "Peace be unto you.. do not be afraid."
        Jesus breathes on them and gives them the power to forgive sin.

        Dear Jesus, You resurrected after 3 days in the tomb as you have said you would.
        And when you resurrected you didn't make it a big deal and tell all those who doubted you to see what you did.
        In all humility and simplicity you did what you had to without showing off. You thought us simplicity,
        all that matters is to seek  your approval patiently not of human,
        to do our tasks in simplicity no matter how big they are, or who they prove wrong or right.
        You told us that we will know a tree by its fruits. You also comforted us in trusting every word you said by
        resurrecting as you said. Please help the whole humanity to know who saved them and who to trust.
        You love us so much and you want us to trust you fully and be under your protection.
        We have a God who is so powerful and capable to resolve all our problems, no one should leave in fear or desperation.
        You are more than capable. Please bring joy into a world that is so sad and lost.
        Bring peace and comfort to the troubled.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_ascension">
        "Jesus remains on earth forty days after His Resurrection to prove He has truly risen from the dead.
        He commissions the apostles to preach the gospel to every creature, and promises to be with them forever.
        He will not leave them orphans, but will send the Holy Spirit to enlighten and strengthen them.
        Jesus proceeds to Mt. Olivet accompanied by His Mother and the apostles and disciples.
        Extending His pierced hands over all in a last blessing, He ascends into heaven.
        As He ascends a cloud takes Him from their sight.
        Jesus ascends to take His place at the right hand of the Father.
        What jubilation there must be amid the angels of heaven at the triumphant entry of Jesus.
        The wounds in His glorified body are an endless plea before the Father on our behalf.
        The disciples leave Mt. Olivet and "return to Jerusalem with great joy."

        Dear Jesus, You resurrected as you said and you went back to heaven as you said in front of your disciples.
        What touches most, before you rose from earth you comforted your disciples and told them that you are not leaving them
        alone but you are going to prepare a place for them so they can join you later to live eternally happy.
        You sent them to spread the good news that you are the way, the truth and the life.
        That the one who believes in you shall not die and will eternally happy. And they you cared to remind them
        that you will send them the Holy Spirit to strengthen them in the mission you have them.
        I thank you for that when we think we are alone, or tired, not capable, you have thought about everything
        we will need and you provide. We love you Jesus and we want to fully trust you and love you more.
        Please give us the strength necessary to see, to love you, to help you be your messengers among your
        children in the world so we can continue to help you save the world.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_descent">
        "The apostles are gathered in the upper room where Jesus had held the Last Supper.
        They are persevering in prayer with Mary the Mother of Jesus.
        A sound comes from heaven like the rush of a mighty wind, and it fills the whole house.
        The Holy Spirit descends on each of them in the form of tongues of fire.
        Filled with the Gifts of the Holy Spirit, they are enlightened and strengthened to spread the Gospel.
        Having lost all fear of the Jewish leaders, the apostles boldly preach Christ crucified.
        The multitudes are confounded because every man hears them speak in his own tongue.
        The Holy Spirit comes upon the Infant Church never to leave it.
        That first day Peter goes forth to preach and baptizes three thousand.
        The feast of Pentecost is the birthday of the Church, for on that day it begins to grow.

        Dear Jesus, You went back to celebrate your accomplishment on earth, saving us and living back in your paradise.
        But you didn't forget our little strengths. You kept your promise to send the Holy Spirit to your disciples.
        Sending the Holy Spirit to all of us who will need His help and strength. Today the Holy Spirit is still with us,
        especially when we need Him for clarity, to enlighten the way, to love ourselves and love one another,
        to heal us in soul and body, to help us to understand God's ways etc. Dear Jesus, please send me the Holy Spirit,
        to help me in many needs of my hearts, those I am aware of and those I am not aware of.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_assumption">
        "After the apostles have dispersed, the Blessed Mother goes to live with John, the beloved disciple.
        Mary lives many years on earth after the death of Christ.
        She is a source of comfort, consolation and strength to the apostles.
        As she had nourished the infant Jesus, so she nourishes spiritually the infant Church.
        Mary dies, not of bodily infirmity, but is wholly overcome in a rapture of divine love.
        Her body as well as her soul is taken up into heaven.
        After her burial the apostles go to the tomb and find only fragrant lilies.
        Jesus does not permit the sinless body of His Mother to decay in the grave.
        Corruption of the body is an effect of original sin from which Mary is totally exempted.
        The bodies of all mankind, at the last judgment, will be brought back and united again to the soul.

        Dear Blessed Virgin Mary, You have pleased God so much in your life. You have done His Will to the perfection,
        and because you have placed nearest to the Holy Trinity. You were chosen to be Jesus' Mother because you were so pure.
        You never condemned anyone, you said a bad word about anyone. You always wanted to help those in need,
        protect their dignity and reputation. You are our perfect model on how to live this life and how to love God
        and others to the best. Please mother who was given to us to be our own mother. Teach us how to be like you,
        to make good choices in our lives to follow God's ways. Pray for us so that we have enough discernment to
        recognize the truth. More than anything so many people are broken by so much injustice, lack of love, loneliness,
        rejection etc.. please awaken our hearts to know how much God loves us, how much you love us.
        You said in the past that if we knew how much we are loved, we would cry of joy. Our hearts have been so hardened,
        we don't feel it as it is. Pray for us mother.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_coronation">
        "As Mary enters heaven, the entire court of heaven greets with joy this masterpiece of God's creation.
        Mary is crowned by her divine Son as Queen of heaven and earth.
        More than we can ever know the Hearts of Jesus and Mary overflow with joy at this reunion.
        Only in heaven will we know the great majesty of that coronation, and the joy it gave to the angels and saints.
        Even the angels, who by nature are greater than humans, hail Mary as their Queen.
        Mary shares so fully in the glory of Christ because she shared so fully in His suffering.
        Only in heaven will we see how central is the role of Mary in the divine plan of redemption.
        The angels and saints longed for the coming of her whose heel crushes the head of the serpent.
        Mary pleads our cause as a most powerful Queen and a most merciful and loving Mother.
        A great sign appeared in heaven; a woman clothed with the sun, the moon under her feet, and on her head a crown of twelve stars.

        Dear Blessed Virgin Mary, You became the queen of heaven and earth as a reward of how you lived your life so lovingly
        and purely. Oh mother we know everyone who lives their lives lovingly and correctly will also know so much joy in heaven,
        eternally. You are now our Mother and our Queen, which make us princesses and princes!
        Mother why do we even ever worry about anything when we have the one who loves us this much,
        and who can give us whatever we ask for? But mother what we need most is love and light in this world,
        please pleas to Jesus for is to give it to us, He can never say no to you. Pray for us as you always do
        and open our hearts to the truth of the love of God for us and help us to love Him back and appreciate Him. We love you.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_baptism">
        "John is baptizing in the Jordan proclaiming a baptism of repentance.
        "I am the voice of one crying in the desert, make straight the way of the Lord."
        "One mightier than I is coming after me."
        "I have baptized you with water, He will baptize you with the Holy Spirit."
        Seeing Jesus, John exclaims: "Behold the Lamb of God."
        Against protests of his unworthiness, John baptizes Jesus in the Jordan.
        After Jesus' baptism a voice from Heaven: "This is my beloved Son in whom I am well pleased."
        The Spirit descends upon Jesus in the form of a dove.
        In this heavenly manifestation is instituted the sacrament of baptism.
        The divine Trinity is manifested: the voice of the Father is heard as the Spirit descends upon the Son. stars.

        Dear Jesus, you showed us how important our sacraments are by getting baptized yourself even if you didn't need it.
        You were one with the Father always. Even at the baptism, He spoke from heaven,
        "This is my beloved Son in whom I am well pleased"! You are the Way, Truth and Life,
        help me to see your light and have the wisdom and courage to follow you.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_cana">
        "Jesus, His Mother and disciples were invited to a wedding in Cana.
        During the wedding feast the wine ran short.
        Mary turned to Jesus: "They have no wine."
        Jesus replied: "What would you have Me do? My hour has not yet come."
        Mary said to the waiters: "Do whatever He tells you."
        There were six stone water jars, each holding fifteen to twenty gallons.
        Jesus bids the waiters to fill the jars with water, and then draw some out and take it to the chief steward.
        The chief steward said to the groom: "Every man serves the good wine first.. but you have saved the good wine until now."
        At Mary's request, Jesus worked His first miracle.
        By His presence, Christian marriage was raised to the dignity of a Sacrament.

        Dear Jesus, your Mother told you about the need for wine at the wedding,
        you told her it was not yet the time for you to perform miracles, but out of compassion and love for your mother,
        you performed a miracle by changing the water into wine, because She asked. You changed water into wine,
        not just any wine but the best wine, better than what they had before and you did it privately.
        People were surprised that the host of the wedding served better wine at the end.
        My dear Jesus grant me the grace to see the role of Mary in my life, to ask her for help when I am in need.
        Because you love her so much, and she loves me so much as a mother. You know the desires of my heart,
        if you change water into wine, I trust that you can change my sorrow into joy, my failures into triumph,
        help me with the help of Mary to seek to please you first, to live a peaceful life,
        to be a loving hand that reaches out to my brothers and sisters always,
        all else will be added to me.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_proclamation">
        ""Repent, for the kingdom of God is at hand."
        "My kingdom is not of this world."
        "Unless a man be born again of water and the Spirit, he cannot enter the kingdom of heaven."
        "Whoever does not accept the kingdom of God as a little child will not enter into it."
        "I have come to call sinners, not the just."
        "Love your enemies, pray for those who persecute you."
        "Blessed are the poor in spirit, for theirs is the kingdom of heaven."
        "Blessed are they who hunger and thirst for justice, for they shall be satisfied."
        "Blessed are they who suffer persecution for justice sake, for theirs is the kingdom of heaven."
        "You are Peter, and upon this rock I will build My church.. I will give you the keys of the kingdom of heaven."

        Dear Jesus, you left your heaven, your paradise to come to live with us, to come to teach us,
        no matter how high the cost to you, the suffering you would go through.
        You accepted it so you could teach me how to love and live a life detached from earthly good so I could
        earn a place in heaven and live eternally happy.  Thank you for everything you did for us,
        please give me humility to be able to listen to you and understand what you mean.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_transfiguration">
        "Jesus took Peter, James and John up a high mountain to pray.
        Jesus was transfigured before them.
        "His face became as dazzling as the sun, his clothes as radiant as light."
        This was to fortify their faith to withstand the coming tragedy of the Passion.
        Jesus foresaw the 'scandal of the cross,' and prepared them for it by this manifestation of His glory.
        Moses and Elias (representing the Law and the prophets of the Old Testament) were conversing with Jesus about His Passion.
        "Do not think I have come to destroy the Law or the Prophets.. but to fulfill them."
        From a cloud came a voice: "This is my beloved Son, listen to Him."
        Jesus admonishes them not to tell the vision to anyone until the Son of Man rises from the dead.
        We too will behold the transfigured Jesus on the Last Day.

        Dear Jesus, you called Peter, James and John to go with you on the mountain, when you got there,
        you transformed into light, then Alijaah and Moses appeared beside you.
        Peter was so surprised and felt the joy of heaven and asked if you could all stay there.
        Then the voice of God said again, "this is my beloved Son in whom I am well pleased! Listen to Him"!
        What a joy Jesus to be with you! What touched my heart is that you did this to strengthen the disciples
        for what was going to follow. You would be beaten up, you would be shamed,
        you would give yourself willingly without resistance.  Facing all that you were able to think of your
        disciples who might be confused when they witnessed it, especially the one who would be the rock,
        on which you would build your church, Peter. Thank you for understanding our weaknesses,
        please help me to never deny you, to see you in everyone, to feel your presence always.
        Help me to be patient with myself when I need it. Help me to be humble enough to rely on your guidance in this life.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="rosary_english_eucharist">
        "I have eagerly desired to eat this Passover with you before I suffer.
        Jesus took bread, blessed it: "Take and eat, this is My Body."
        Taking the wine: "This cup is the new covenant in my Blood, shed for you."
        At that eucharistic meal, Jesus celebrated the first Mass.
        At every Mass the sacrifice of Calvary is made present.
        At the Last Supper Jesus instituted the sacrament of Holy Orders to perpetuate this sacrifice.
        "Whoever eats my flesh and drinks my blood remains in me and I in him."
        The Eucharist is a sacrifice inasmuch as it is offered up, and a sacrament inasmuch as it is received.
        In the Mass we offer ourselves to God, and God gives himself to us.
        The Mass will be fruitful in the measure of our surrender to the Father.

        Dear Jesus, before you were put to death you still had to remember to give us the Eucharist through which you
        would remain with us eternally because you loved us that much. At the table where you shared your heritage with us,
        was Judas who would betray you and Peter who would deny you. Yet you didn't push anyone away,
        you didn't exclude anyone from taking part in your gifts. Thank you, and please help me to love everyone,
        to be fair in all I do, and to love you and see you in the Eucharist.

        <b>\nOur Father.. \t\t10Hail Mary"'"s \t\tGlory be.."</b>

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_normal_english_rosary">NormalEnglishRosary</string>
    <string name="title_activity_normal_malayalam_rosary">NormalMalayalamRosary</string>
</resources>
